<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<ValueSet xmlns="http://hl7.org/fhir">
  <text>
    <status value="generated"/>
    <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <h2>GeneralPurposeOfUse</h2>
      <p> Supports communication of purpose of use at a general level. (OID = 2.16.840.1.113883.1.11.20449)</p>
      <p>This value set includes codes defined in other code systems, using the following rules:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Include these codes as defined in 
          <a href="../../../v3/ActReason/index.html">http://hl7.org/fhir/v3/ActReason</a>
          <table>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <b>Code</b>
              </td>
              <td>
                <b>Display</b>
              </td>
              <td>
                <b>Definition</b>
              </td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>COVERAGE</td>
              <td>coverage under policy or program</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information for conducting activities related to coverage under a program or policy.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>ETREAT</td>
              <td>Emergency Treatment</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information for provision of immediately needed health care for an emergent condition.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>HMARKT</td>
              <td>healthcare marketing</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information for marketing services and products related to health care.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>HOPERAT</td>
              <td>healthcare operations</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information used for conducting administrative and contractual activities related to the provision of health care.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>HPAYMT</td>
              <td>healthcare payment</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information for conducting financial or contractual activities related to payment for provision of health care.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>HRESCH</td>
              <td>healthcare research</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information for conducting scientific investigations to obtain health care knowledge.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>PATRQT</td>
              <td>patient requested</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information in response to a patient&#39;s request.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>PUBHLTH</td>
              <td>public health</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information for conducting public health activities, such as the reporting of notifiable conditions.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>TREAT</td>
              <td>treatment</td>
              <td>To perform one or more operations on information for provision of health care.</td>
            </tr>
          </table>
        </li>
      </ul>
    </div>
  </text>
  <identifier value="http://hl7.org/fhir/v3/vs/GeneralPurposeOfUse"/>
  <version value="2013-12-07"/>
  <name value="GeneralPurposeOfUse"/>
  <publisher value="HL7 v3"/>
  <telecom>
    <system value="url"/>
    <value value="http://www.hl7.org"/>
  </telecom>
  <description value=" Supports communication of purpose of use at a general level. (OID = 2.16.840.1.113883.1.11.20449)"/>
  <status value="active"/>
  <compose>
    <include>
      <system value="http://hl7.org/fhir/v3/ActReason"/>
      <code value="COVERAGE"/>
      <code value="ETREAT"/>
      <code value="HMARKT"/>
      <code value="HOPERAT"/>
      <code value="HPAYMT"/>
      <code value="HRESCH"/>
      <code value="PATRQT"/>
      <code value="PUBHLTH"/>
      <code value="TREAT"/>
    </include>
  </compose>
</ValueSet>